export const questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "A car covers a certain distance at 60 km/h and returns at 80 km/h. What is the average speed of the car for the whole journey?",
    options: ["68 km/h", "69 km/h", "70 km/h", "72 km/h"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "Simplify: 8/15 + 7/20 - 11/30",
    options: ["17/60", "19/60", "21/60", "23/60"],
    correctAnswer: 2  
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "A train 150 m long crosses a man walking at 5 km/h in 9 seconds. Find the trainâ€™s speed in km/h.",
    options: ["50 km/h", "55 km/h", "60 km/h", "65 km/h"],
    correctAnswer: 3
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Simplify: (14)^2 - (9)^2 + (6*5)",
    options: ["100", "110", "120", "130"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "A cyclist travels 40 km in 4 hours partly uphill at 8 km/h and partly downhill at 12 km/h. Find the distance traveled uphill.",
    options: ["12 km", "15 km", "18 km", "20 km"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id:6,
    question:"If (3/7)x + (5/14)x = 64, find x",
    options: ["56","64","72","84"],
    correctAnswer: 4
  },
  {
    id:7,
    question:"A boat goes 12 km downstream in 40 minutes and returns in 1 hour. Find the speed of the boat in still water.",
    options: ["10 km/h","11 km/h","12 km/h","13 km/h"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id:8,
    question:"Simplify: ((0.5)^3 + (0.2)^3)/(0.5*0.2)",
    options: ["0.73","0.85","0.94","1.0"],
    correctAnswer: 3
  },
  {
    id:9,
    question:"Two friends start from the same point. One walks north at 5 km/h, the other east at 12 km/h. How far apart will they be after 2 hours?",
    options: ["20 km","22 km","24 km","26 km"],
    correctAnswer: 4
  },
  {
    id:10,
    question:"Simplify: (144/sqrt(144)) + sqrt(225)",
    options: ["22","24","26","28"],
    correctAnswer: 3
  },
  {
    id:11,
    question:"A train leaves City A at 6:00 AM at 60 km/h. Another train leaves City B towards A at 7:00 AM at 80 km/h. The cities are 300 km apart. At what time will they meet?",
    options: ["8:30 AM","8:45 AM","9:00 AM","9:15 AM"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id:12,
    question:"Simplify: 3(1/4)*2(2/3)",
    options: ["8.5","8.6","8.666...","8.75"],
    correctAnswer: 3
  },
  {
    id:13,
    question:"A man walks 1 km in 12 minutes. How many kilometers will he walk in 2 hours 24 minutes?",
    options: ["12 km","13 km","14 km","15 km"],
    correctAnswer: 3
  },
  {
    id:14,
    question:"Simplify: 5/12+7/18",
    options: ["43/36","53/36","61/36","67/36"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id:15,
    question:"A car travels 150 km at a uniform speed. If the speed had been 10 km/h more, it would have taken 30 minutes less. Find the speed.",
    options: ["40 km/h","45 km/h","50 km/h","60 km/h"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id:16,
    question:"Simplify: 18(2/3) / 2(1/2)",
    options: ["7.25","7.4","7.45","7.5"],
    correctAnswer: 4
  },
];